nutritionfacts.org exists because of
you. Every book, every video, every
webinar only happens because we have
supporters like you to keep us going.
Without your support, none of this would
exist. So, as we close out this year, I
do need your help. This is when we raise
at least half of our annual budget so we
can continue providing free
evidence-based health nutrition
information to the world. So, it's
always a little nerve-wracking
until the end. But you have never let us
down. If uh so if nutritionfacts.org has
helped you or someone you love, uh
please consider making a taxdeductible
donation today. Gifts of any size make a
difference, but becoming a monthly donor
to a nonprofit charity is particularly
helpful to uh kind of giving us a steady
support so uh we can rely on so we don't
have to wait for the end ofear
nailbiter. Uh together we can make this
another year of researching and
disseminating lifesaving information to
the world. Root for the facts by helping
us fill the carrot.